

BASIC

INFORMATION

Birth: 30th November 1998, Dubai Languages known: English and Hindi

ABOUT ME

I try to grasp and hold as much of life as a 21-year-old possibly could. My optimism comes from the constant construction of reality based on films and television shows I watch. I try to photo document every little amusing factor I find throughout the day. I enjoy constantly indulging myself in debates and discussions related to science and politics.

Skills

Creativity – Perseverance – Communication Responsibility - Leadership

Certified MOOC Courses

- The Fundamentals of Digital Marketing
 Google Digital Garage
- Introduction to Psychology University of Toronto

ANIL NAIR

Kharghar, Navi Mumbai phone: +(91) 9699193366 email: anlnir@hotmail.com

Experience

White Rivers Media

Content Writer, August 2019 to February 2020

Worked as a copywriter, writing primarily for a leading pub chain with over 22 outlets all over India. Have also written long-form content for insurance companies, broadband services and analytical data companies.

AIESEC, Hungary

Assistant Teacher, April 2017 to June 2017

A 40-day global volunteer program in Hungary, helping to progress the 'Sustainable Development Goal' of 'Quality Education', affiliated to the United Nations.

Spectrum

Editor

Edited and wrote articles for the English section of an award winning college magazine 'Spectrum', winning the 'Best Editor 2018' award.

Other Noteworthy Work

Worked with the theatre group in school. Also worked for the college fest 'Alegria', organising and executing events related to the performing arts.

Education

Pillai College of Arts, Commerce & Science

Bachelor of Mass Media (BMM) – June 2016 to April 2019 [Grade: A]

Bal Bharati Public School

12th Grade: PCB & Mass Media, completed in 2016, scoring 69.98%

10th Grade: CBSE, completed in 2014, scoring 8.6 CGPA